{
  "allQuestions": [
    {
      "question": "Which New York newspaper’s building and lobby stood in for The Daily Planet in Superman?",
      "answer": [
        "New York Daily Today",
        "New York Daily Times",
        "New York Daily Post",
        "New York Daily News"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "New York Daily News"
    },
    {
      "question": "In Superman, where does Lex Luthor set up his lair?",
      "answer": [
        "In disused parts of the Lexcorp office tower",
        "Atop the Chrysler Building (or the Metropolis equivalent)",
        "In a forgotten, but opulent Metropolis train station",
        "In the sciences building at Metropolis State University"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "In a forgotten, but opulent Metropolis train station"
    },
    {
      "question": "In Superman Returns, what is the name Lex Luthor gives his new landmass off the coast of Metropolis?",
      "answer": [
        "Lextopia",
        "New Metropolis",
        "New Krypton",
        "Vista del Lex"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "New Krypton"
    },
    {
      "question": "In Superman, what song is playing in Brad’s car as Clark runs up to the Kent farm?",
      "answer": [
        "“Rock Around the Clock”",
        "“See You Later, Alligator”",
        "“Crazy Man, Crazy”",
        "“Shake, Rattle and Roll”"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "“Rock Around the Clock”"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Metropolis’s nickname according to Superman III?",
      "answer": [
        "The Big Apricot",
        "The City of Tomorrow",
        "The City That Never Shuts Downr",
        "The Big Lemon Drop"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "The Big Apricot"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following actors was not cast as Dick Grayson in a Batman film?",
      "answer": [
        "Jerry O’Connell",
        "Marlon Wayans",
        "Chris O’Donnell",
        "Ricky Addison Reed"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Jerry O’Connell"
    },
    {
      "question": "The 1989 Batmobile was built over which make and model of car?",
      "answer": [
        "Jaguar XJS",
        "Pontiac Firebird",
        "Chevy Impala",
        "Ford Mustang"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Chevy Impala"
    },
    {
      "question": "What was the name of Penguin’s gang in Batman Returns?",
      "answer": [
        "The Red Herring Gang",
        "The Red Circle Gang",
        "The Red Gang",
        "The Red Triangle Gang"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "The Red Triangle Gang"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following Batman villains appears in Batman v Superman: Dawn of Justice?",
      "answer": [
        "Killer Moth",
        "KGBeast",
        "Lady Shiva",
        "Anarky"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "KGBeast"
    },
    {
      "question": "Before he became Cyborg, Vic Stone played football for which college?",
      "answer": [
        "Gotham City University",
        "Gotham State University",
        "Smallville A&M",
        "Metropolis College"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Gotham City University"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which DC villain is Justice League big bad Steppenwolf related to?",
      "answer": [
        "Darkseid",
        "Mongul",
        "The Anti-Monitor",
        "Parallax"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Darkseid"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which facility houses the criminals featured in Suicide Squad?",
      "answer": [
        "Iron Heights",
        "Stryker’s Island Penitentiary",
        "Belle Reve Special Security Barracks",
        "Arkham Asylum"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Belle Reve Special Security Barracks"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which villain makes a brief cameo in the Justice League stinger scene?",
      "answer": [
        "Deathbringer",
        "Deathstroke",
        "Deathstorm",
        "Deadshot"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Deathstroke"
    }
  ]
}
